widgetsplus.com 2018-01-04

# Google+ Widget :: Google Plus customizable Widget to get in touch with your visitors

In this privacy statement Widgets Plus want to inform you about the purposes for wich Widgets Plus will use your personal information and under wich circumstances we collect them. Widgets Plus respects and protects the privacy of all users of the site Widget Plus. Widgets Plus is committed to fairness in order to ensure that all personal information it receives will be treated as confidential and will only be used for the purposes as described in this Privacy Statement

**Purposes** We store your information to get a faster service. We chache your file on our server and refresh them every 4 hours. Next to that we store some information ( like follower count, name, and widget is hosted on) to develop and publish new things for Widgets Plus, some of your information can be used on public pages of the Widgets Plus website. 

**Your personal information** Your personal information is not available to third parties. We appreciate your confidence in us, and we will do everything to protect your personal information. If you run the widget on your blog we daily store information like followers and your short description. The only things we use in the public area of the website are things you have set to public in Google Plus and statistics of your Widget.

**Links** Our sites may contain links to the websites of our subsidiary companies, partners and to the websites of third parties. These sites may have a different Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected through this website. We are not responsible for compliance of our partners or other parties of the privacy legislation.

**Questions or requests** On request we will remove your details from our database or modify. If you have questions or comments regarding to our privacy policy and the way we treat personal information, please email us at: [info@widgetsplus.com](mailto:info@widgetsplus.com)

**Miscellaneous** The Privacy Statement can be adjusted by Widgets Plus at any time. Widgets Plus advises to check the Privacy Statement regularly.

**Privacy Statement** This site is managed by Widgets Plus. During your visit of this website Widgets Plus will collect personal data about you, either directly (through a request for data) or indirectly. Widgets Plus will only use personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement and will do everything to protect the personal information collected. This Privacy Statement sets out the purposes of Widgets Plus at processing data associated with this website and about your rights regarding your personal information.

**Purposes of processing** Widgets Plus collects and processes information about visitors of this website to run the services we deliver and create new services.

**Sensitive information** Widgets Plus does not seek to collect sensitive personal data through this website such as data revealing political opinions, religious beliefs, health or other issues!
